playkidsgames.com 2018-10-11

# Play Kids' Games -- Kids Games On Line - kids games, alphabet games, math games, letter games, addition games, subraction games, K12, education, multiplication games, division games, letter, alphabet, spelling , learning games, educational games, word, java games, applets, children, kids, child games, child, spelling, games, alphabet,baby, kids.com, learning, www.play, kids games to play, games to play

##  Privacy Statement for Play Kids Games 

**Play Kids Games** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Play Kids Games ](http://www.playkidsgames.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. _This is to better understand our target audience._

####  Advertisers 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.   
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  

####  Personal Information 

We do not require any personal information on this Web site. If e-mail address or any other personal information is given for feedback or mailing, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes other than to resond to your inquiries. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Play Kids Games** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. _Only authorized users have access to edit this web site. Any e-mail information is kept outside of this web site and is on a private server._

####  Children's Guidelines 

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent 
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
